DMITRY NASANOVICH

PYTHON DEVELOPER

+380677702977

auditor.rst@gmail.com

26n.github.com

Odessa Ukraina 🕞

PROFILE



I've been actively learning Python for a year now, completed two courses at stepik.org, and received certifications.

I made several projects on writing telegram bots which you can find on GitHub. I can work with Database & SQL, FTP, SSH, Docker, set up projects on VDS\Unix systems, worked with asynchronous programming as well: aiogram, webhook, os, etc. Have a basic knowledge of HTML and CSS. At the moment I'm studying Django and increasing the level of knowledge gained.

EXPERIENCE

2020 - 2022 Mining BTC.com

Connection and service. Installing software, monitoring the performance and correct operation of the equipment. Periodic maintenance of hash boards.

2016 - 2020 VOIP

Termination of telephone traffic from the network to the cells of the mobile operator. Installation of specialized software and hardware. Control of the correct operation and quality sound transmission.

2014 - 2016 Sales Technician

Advising customers on the properties, quality and service of goods. Sold various goods, such as: TVs, cell phones, laptops, cameras, small appliances

MY SKILLS		LANGUAGES
		
Python	VPN & VDS	English
Unix	HTML / CSS	Italian ——
WordPress	Database / SQL	Ukrainian
Docker	Photoshop	Russian

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022 Generation Python : beginner course Generation Python : advanced course

• I took both courses with practice at stepik.org and received certificates. Practiced for a year and continue to improve my skills.

1997 - 2001 Manager Secondary special education College of Commerce and Enterprise College of retail and wholesale trade. I have studied for 4 years. Leading subjects: marketing, economics, management